[{"answer": " Whats the matter, Monica?  You seem like you have something on your mind", "docId": "07-05", "aSentId": 12, "question": "", "qSentId": 11},{"answer": " Oh, its nothing", "docId": "07-05", "aSentId": 13, "question": " Whats the matter, Monica?  You seem like you have something on your mind", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " Come on.  Tell me.  I can tell something is bothering you", "docId": "07-05", "aSentId": 14, "question": " Oh, its nothing", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " All right.  Its about Beth.  You know, weve been best friends for like 15 year", "docId": "07-05", "aSentId": 15, "question": " Come on.  Tell me.  I can tell something is bothering you", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " Yeah, you guys have always been close", "docId": "07-05", "aSentId": 19, "question": " All right.  Its about Beth.  You know, weve been best friends for like 15 year", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " I know.  But this week she did something and I dont know if I can be friend", "docId": "07-05", "aSentId": 20, "question": " Yeah, you guys have always been close", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " What happened", "docId": "07-05", "aSentId": 24, "question": " I know.  But this week she did something and I dont know if I can be friend", "qSentId": 23},{"answer": " Well, do you remember Dave?  The guy I used to date", "docId": "07-05", "aSentId": 25, "question": " What happened", "qSentId": 24},{"answer": " The one that played soccer?  He was cute", "docId": "07-05", "aSentId": 26, "question": " Well, do you remember Dave?  The guy I used to date", "qSentId": 25},{"answer": " No, not that guy.  That was Paul", "docId": "07-05", "aSentId": 30, "question": " The one that played soccer?  He was cute", "qSentId": 29},{"answer": " Oh", "docId": "07-05", "aSentId": 31, "question": " No, not that guy.  That was Paul", "qSentId": 30},{"answer": " Dave was the guy I dated like six years ago.  He was tall and had a big tatto", "docId": "07-05", "aSentId": 32, "question": " Oh", "qSentId": 31},{"answer": " Oh, yeah.  I think I remember him", "docId": "07-05", "aSentId": 36, "question": " Dave was the guy I dated like six years ago.  He was tall and had a big tatto", "qSentId": 35},{"answer": " Yeah.  We dated for about six months.  Anyways, last weekend Beth and ", "docId": "07-05", "aSentId": 37, "question": " Oh, yeah.  I think I remember him", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " Did you guys talk to him", "docId": "07-05", "aSentId": 41, "question": " Yeah.  We dated for about six months.  Anyways, last weekend Beth and ", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": " I did a little.  But listen to what happened.  We had been at the party for abou", "docId": "07-05", "aSentId": 42, "question": " Did you guys talk to him", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": " Really?  What did you do", "docId": "07-05", "aSentId": 46, "question": " I did a little.  But listen to what happened.  We had been at the party for abou", "qSentId": 45},{"answer": " Nothing.  What could I do?  I just left the party without saying anything to them", "docId": "07-05", "aSentId": 47, "question": " Really?  What did you do", "qSentId": 46},{"answer": " Oh, well have you talked to Beth since", "docId": "07-05", "aSentId": 51, "question": " Nothing.  What could I do?  I just left the party without saying anything to them", "qSentId": 50},{"answer": " No.  Shes been calling me and texting me all week.  Shes wondering why I", "docId": "07-05", "aSentId": 52, "question": " Oh, well have you talked to Beth since", "qSentId": 51},{"answer": " But you guys have been best friends for so long", "docId": "07-05", "aSentId": 56, "question": " No.  Shes been calling me and texting me all week.  Shes wondering why I", "qSentId": 55},{"answer": " I know.  But how can I be friends with her still after she betrayed me like that", "docId": "07-05", "aSentId": 57, "question": " But you guys have been best friends for so long", "qSentId": 56},{"answer": " Well, you said its been six years since you dated Dave.  Thats a pretty long time", "docId": "07-05", "aSentId": 62, "question": " I know.  But how can I be friends with her still after she betrayed me like that", "qSentId": 61},{"answer": " No, not really.  We never really had much in common", "docId": "07-05", "aSentId": 66, "question": " Well, you said its been six years since you dated Dave.  Thats a pretty long time", "qSentId": 65},{"answer": " Well, it seems like you didnt like him much and it was a really long time ago tha", "docId": "07-05", "aSentId": 67, "question": " No, not really.  We never really had much in common", "qSentId": 66},{"answer": " I don know.  Im not sure what to do", "docId": "07-05", "aSentId": 71, "question": " Well, it seems like you didnt like him much and it was a really long time ago tha", "qSentId": 70},{"answer": " Guys are going to come and go in your lives, but true friends will stay together", "docId": "07-05", "aSentId": 75, "question": " I don know.  Im not sure what to do", "qSentId": 74},{"answer": " I guess youre right.  I dont want to lose our friendship over something silly lik", "docId": "07-05", "aSentId": 79, "question": " Guys are going to come and go in your lives, but true friends will stay together", "qSentId": 78},{"answer": " Why dont you call Beth and talk to her?  Im sure she didnt mean to upset you", "docId": "07-05", "aSentId": 83, "question": " I guess youre right.  I dont want to lose our friendship over something silly lik", "qSentId": 82},{"answer": " Youre right.  I should.  Ill call her tonight", "docId": "07-05", "aSentId": 84, "question": " Why dont you call Beth and talk to her?  Im sure she didnt mean to upset you", "qSentId": 83},{"answer": " Good.  I think thats the right thing to do", "docId": "07-05", "aSentId": 85, "question": " Youre right.  I should.  Ill call her tonight", "qSentId": 84},{"answer": " Thanks for listening and for your helpful advice", "docId": "07-05", "aSentId": 86, "question": " Good.  I think thats the right thing to do", "qSentId": 85},{"answer": " Youre welcome.  Anytime", "docId": "07-05", "aSentId": 87, "question": " Thanks for listening and for your helpful advice", "qSentId": 86}]
